kalixa.com 2014-07-04

# Kalixa Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Kalixa is brought to you by Kalixa Pay Ltd (Kalixa Pay), who is committed to protecting your privacy. All data is collected, transferred, processed and maintained in accordance with the principles contained within the Data Protection Act 1998 of the United Kingdom and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. We recognise our responsibility to keep your information confidential and secure. Any personal information about you which we obtain in connection with your Kalixa Card registration and eAccount operation, we undertake to keep safe. We will not share this information with other people or businesses, other than stated in this policy, without your prior consent.

**The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you.**

### How we collect and use information

To enable us to issue your Kalixa Card and set up your eAccount, we need to obtain information at registration which includes your name, your e-mail and home addresses, and other relevant personal details.

As a registered user, you have the option to change or revise your personal data (with the exception of your user name, first name, last name, date of birth and country) at any time. After logging in to the Website, you may change your information in the Personal Details area of My Profile.

The information that you provide will only be used for the purposes described at the time of your registration and where applicable in the Terms and Conditions that apply to the relevant product or service. We will also collect, store and process your personal information on our computers to develop and improve our overall service to you, communicate with you and to manage your eAccount.

We give access to your personal information only to those employees who require it to provide our services.

If you do not want to receive marketing communication , please log in to your account and manage your settings for communications.

We will not disclose any such information outside of Kalixa Pay except in the limited circumstances described below, as permitted by applicable law, or with your express permission:

• To fraud prevention agencies and other organisations who may use the information to prevent fraud and money laundering, or in order to assist us in investigating suspected violations of our Terms and Condition

• To persons acting as our agents under a strict code of confidentiality

• To anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer our rights and duties under our Terms and Conditions with you

• As required by law or regulation

To fulfil some of the above processes we may have to pass your information to other parts of our group of companies, which may be in other countries. We will make sure that they agree to apply the same levels of protection as we are required to apply to information held in the UK and to use your information only for the purpose of providing the service to us.

As with any other business, it is possible that Kalixa Pay in the future could amalgamate or merge with or be acquired by another company. If such acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the personal information maintained by Kalixa Pay, including customer eAccount information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described above.

### How we apply our policy

In order to put our policy into practice, we use our best endeavours to follow these guidelines:

  * We will ensure our systems are secure to protect your personal information from misuse 
  * We will not hold your personal information for longer than is necessary 
  * We will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to other people or businesses unless we have your consent; with your consent, we will only share your information with carefully chosen, reputable and trustworthy third parties 
  * We will comply promptly with any instructions from you to update your information or requests from you to see the information that we hold on you 
  * We will comply with lawful requests to disclose personal information to certain authorities (e.g. the police) 
  * We may monitor and record any telephone calls to ensure we follow your instructions correctly and to improve our service 

If you would like a copy of the information we hold about you, please write to: Kalixa Pay Ltd., PO Box 72074, London EC4P 4GB, United Kingdom. There will be an administration charge of £12 for this service.

### Links to other websites

This Website includes links to other websites. These are outside our control and not covered by this policy. If you access those websites via the links, use of those websites will be in accordance with the privacy policy of those website operators, which may differ from ours.

### Data encryption and Technical Security Measures

To protect your personal data during communication with your web browser, Kalixa Pay’s payment provider, CQR Payment Solutions GmbH, uses secure and tested encryption technology from VeriSign®. Online transactions are protected by the extremely reliable security system of a worldwide-accredited partner.

To prevent the illegal manipulation through a third person, the IP address of the logged-on computer will be requested and saved. In addition, all your data is protected from unauthorised access by a firewall – a computer that is fitted with complex security technology specifically designed to shield the company’s network from the Internet. Additionally, the company uses reliable internal data protection mechanisms combined with a restrictive security system.

### Cookies

During the course of your visit to our Website, your computer may be issued with cookies. Cookies are text files which identify your computer to a server. Cookies do not in themselves identify you as an individual, just the computer you are using. We do not collect or store any personally identifiable information using the cookie.

Cookies are commonly used on the Internet and do not harm your system.  
Cookies have a number of uses. For example, cookies are part of the mechanism that allows you to log in and out of our Website rather than having to enter your password repeatedly during a session. They can also be used to estimate the number of users to our Website. Cookies may also be used for other purposes, such as to maintain the security of the Website and provide information on what administrative support the Website may require. 

The cookies used on [http://www.kalixa.com](http://www.kalixa.com/) and [https://secure.kalixa.com](https://secure.kalixa.com/) fall into three categories which are detailed below:

**Functional** :  
These cookies are used to enable core website functionality and do not contain any personal information.

  * ASP.NET_SessionId  
identifies your computer for the duration of your visit 
  * Epslanguage  
stores your language preference 
  * RegionCode  
stores your region preference 
  * sifrFetch  
allows non-standard fonts to be displayed correctly 

**Analytics:**  
These cookies allow us to count page visits and traffic sources so we can monitor and improve the performance of our Website.

  * .EPiTrace  
used for anonymous analysis of visitor movements around the website 
  * s_cc  
part of Omniture Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * s_sq  
part of Omniture Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * s_vi  
part of Omniture Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * varCook  
part of Omniture Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * __utma  
part of Google Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * __utmb  
part of Google Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * __utmc  
part of Google Analytics package monitoring website usage 
  * __utmz  
part of Google Analytics package monitoring website usage 

**Third Party:**  
We partner with affiliate networks and other websites to help promote Kalixa. If you use their websites, or have come to our site via these affiliates, then their cookies may be set through our website.

  * Atlas  
Atlas tags are used to measure the effectiveness of online marketing campaigns and to provide anonymous transaction data 
  * DoubleClick  
DoubleClick tags are used to measure the effectiveness of online marketing campaigns and to provide anonymous transaction data 
  * Flash Cookie  
used to identify which publisher, website and advertisement a click or transaction originated from 
  * MediaPlex  
MediaPlex tags are used to measure the effectiveness of online marketing campaigns and to provide anonymous transaction data 
  * {value}-MID  
used to identify which publisher, website and advertisement a click or transaction originated from. 

You may delete and block cookies at any time from this site through your browser, but some features on this site will not function without cookies.

You can change the preferences or settings in your web browser to control cookies. In some cases, you can choose to accept cookies from the primary site, but block them from third parties. In others, you can block cookies from specific advertisers, or clear out all cookies.

Microsoft Internet Explorer

  * Help: <http://support.microsoft.com/?ln=en-gb>
  * How to manage Cookies in IE 9: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-GB/windows7/How-to-manage-cookies-in-Internet-Explorer-9>

Mozilla Firefox

  * Help: <http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/home?as=u>
  * Cookies: [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies?s=manage+cookies&r=0&e=es&as=s](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Cookies?s=manage+cookies&r=0&e=es&as=s)

Google Chrome

  * Help: <http://support.google.com/chrome/?hl=en-GB>
  * Manage Cookies: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647)

Our analytics partners also provide the ability for users to opt-out using the following links:  
Omniture Analytics:  
<http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/2o7>  
Google Analytics:  
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

Further information on cookies is available online at: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

We will not sell or distribute cookie information without your prior consent.

### Money Laundering

We are required by law to review transactions and report any which may be suspected of being related to money laundering activities.

### Under 18s

We do not wish to collect any personal information from children under 18. Where we find that a person is under 18, then we will immediately tell them not to provide any personal information to us without their parent or guardian’s permission.

### Changes to this statement

We may change this Privacy Policy to keep up to date with changes in legislation and best practice.

### Notification of changes

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. When changed, we will provide notice to you on our Website that it has been changed.

### Further information

Further information about data protection is available online at the website of the Information Commissioner: www.dataprotection.gov.uk.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Kalixa Pay’s information practices or your dealings with Kalixa Pay, you can contact us at via the contact us page on our Website, or write to us at:

**Kalixa**  
PO Box 72074  
London EC4P 4GB  
United Kingdom
